Let's go back once more to our earlier example where we added
再看看之前的示例
the quick view overlay to the online store front
我们向在线商店中添加了一个快览叠加页面
and flesh out the design details with some terminology.
并用一些术语解释了设计细节
As a reminder, we hypothesized that adding a quick view overlay to
注意 我们假设在用户搜索商品后
the product images after a search might increase the total purchases made by users.
向商品图片上添加快览叠加页面可能会提高用户的总购买量
One thing that you'll want to do is to describe how a user goes from visiting the site,
你需要描述用户如何从访问网站
all the way to finishing their purchase.
一直到完成购买交易
Think about how you would buy something from the site.
思考下你是如何从网站购买商品的
Starting from the homepage,
首先访问首页
you'd put in a product you want into the search bar and get back a list of products.
然后在搜索栏中输入商品 网站随即会显示一个商品列表
After clicking on a product image,
点击商品图片后
you're taken to the product information page.
你将转到商品信息页
Then, you can put the product in your cart and then either keep shopping, or check out.
然后 你可以将商品添加到购物车中 接着要么继续购物 要么结账
This expected path from start to finish is the user funnel.
这种从头到尾的流程称为用户漏斗
How does the funnel change when we implement the new overlay?
如果添加新的叠加页面 用户漏斗会如何变化？
For users in experimental or quick view overlay group,
对于实验组或快览叠加组中的用户
the funnel adds the summary overlays to the product images.
漏斗会向商品图片上添加摘要叠加页面
Users in that condition can use the quick view overlay to add
除了标准商品页之外
products to their cart in addition to the standard product pages.
该组的用户还可以使用快览叠加页面将商品添加到购物车中
Now, we have to decide where in that path to split the users into two groups.
现在 我们需要决定在该流程的什么阶段将用户划分为两组
One way that we could run the experiment is to assign each
一种实验运行方式是
visitor a website cookie as soon as they visit the site.
向访问网站的用户分配一个网站 Cookie
The cookie sticks around through the session and
该 Cookie 在会话中会保留
determines which site version the visitor sees.
用于判断用户访问的是哪个版本的网站
We can describe this method with the term unit of diversion.
我们可以用分组单位一词来描述这种方法
The unit of diversion,
分组单位
in this case the cookie,
在此示例中是指 Cookie
is essentially the place where we divide our observations.
表示划分观察值的位置
From here, we choose our evaluation metrics.
接下来我们将选择评估指标
Metrics upon which we will compare the two groups.
并根据这些指标比较两组数据
These are the values that will tell us if our experiment is a success or not.
这些值将告诉我们实验是否成功了
Examples of good metrics include the total net amount made per user,
好的指标包括每个用户的总净购买量
or just the proportion of visitors who made a purchase in each condition.
或者在每种情形下购买商品的访问者所占比例
We're not limited to just one metric,
我们并非只能使用一个指标
we could track both of them in case the overlay doesn't change them in the same way.
当叠加页面改变两个指标的方式不一样时 我们可以同时跟踪这两种指标
We should also track metrics that we expect to not change between groups.
还可以跟踪预计在两组之间没有变化的指标
These metrics are useful to verify that our control and experimental groups
这些指标可以验证除了要实验的条件之外
are comparable to one another except for the experimental condition.
对照组和实验组之间是对等的
The metrics that just check for these equivalences are called invariant metrics.
检查对等性的指标称为不变指标
An example of an invariant metric in this case
在此示例中 不变指标的示例包括
would be the number of cookies generated by each group.
每组生成的 Cookie 数量
If our randomization is working properly,
如果随机化过程正确的话
then we should expect about the same number of visitors to be assigned to each condition.
那么每种情形分配的访问者人数应该差不多
We can also count the number of logged in users that get assigned to
我们还可以计算分配到每种情形的已登录用户的人数
each condition to control for imbalances in historic shopping behavior.
从而控制历史购买行为带来的影响